I crossed the line
Il-tak
If you don't mind
I'd like to meet up
like this and…
Hey, Lee Hyeon-wu
Don't get the wrong idea
I was just
trying to hide
You're starting
to cross the line
Snap out of it
I'm not your date
Then why did you
stick to me?
You confused me
I should…
tell him the truth
I thought that
if I got close to you
I could escape
Kim Hyeong-ju's
bullying
That's the reason?
Anyone would've
been fine as long as
you achieved your goal
Yeah
Lee Hyeon-wu…
must be furious
Let's head home
Lee Hyeon-wu
Don't make
a face like that
I'm worried
He should've just hit me
I feel horrible
Hey
Why are you
working out so hard?
Mind your own business
I have to do this
or I won't make it
If I could just
beat Lee Hyeon-wu…
Hey, I'm going
to the restroom
Hey
Huh?
Why are you acting out
so much lately?
Huh?
Stop it, you b******